<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Formulas>
  <ABS>
    <Description>Returns the absolute value of a number. The absolute value of a non-negative number is the number itself.</Description>
    <Syntax>ABS(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ABS(10)</Example>
  </ABS>
  <ACCRINT>
    <Description>The ACCRINT function returns the accrued interest for a security with periodic interest payments.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACCRINT(IssueDate,FirstIntrestDate,settlementDate,rate,parvalue,frequency,basis)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACCRINT(G5,G6,G2,G7,E8,F9,0)</Example>
  </ACCRINT>
  <ACCRINTM>
    <Description>The ACCRINTM function returns the accrued interest for a security at maturity..</Description>
    <Syntax>ACCRINT(IssueDate,settlementDate,rate,parvalue,basis)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACCRINTM(G5,G6,G2,G7,E7)</Example>
  </ACCRINTM>  
  <ACOS>
    <Description>Returns the inverse cosine of a number. Inverse cosine is also referred to as arccosine.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACOS(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACOS(1)</Example>
  </ACOS>
  <ACOSH>
    <Description>Returns the inverse hyperbolic cosine of a number. The number must be greater than or equal to 1.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACOSH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACOSH(10)</Example>
  </ACOSH>
  <ACOT>
    <Description>The ACOT function retrieves the principal value of the inverse trigonometric cotangent of a number.To obtain in degrees.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACOT(number) or DEGREES ACOT(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ACOT(45)</Example>
  </ACOT>
  <ACOTH>
    <Description>The ACOTH function retrieves the inverse hyperbolic cotangent of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACOTH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACOTH(90)</Example>
  </ACOTH>
  <ACSCH>
    <Description>The ACSCH function computes the inverse hyperbolic cosecant of its argument.</Description>
    <Syntax>ACSCH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ACSCH(90)</Example>
  </ACSCH>
  <ADDRESS>
    <Description>The ADDRESS function returns the address of a cell in a worksheet given specified row and column numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>ADDRESS(row_num, column_num, [abs_num], [a1],[sheet_text])</Syntax>
    <Example>=ADDRESS(2,3,2,FALSE)</Example>
  </ADDRESS>
  <AND>
    <Description>Returns TRUE if all its arguments evaluate to TRUE; returns FALSE if one or more arguments evaluate to FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>AND(logical1, [logical2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AND(TRUE,TRUE)</Example>
  </AND>
  <ARABIC>
    <Description>A Roman numeral is converted into an Arabic numeral.</Description>
    <Syntax>ARABIC(roman numeral) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ARABIC("XL")</Example>
  </ARABIC>
  <AREAS>
    <Description>The AREAS function returns the number of areas that make up the reference. </Description>
    <Syntax>AREAS(reference) </Syntax>
    <Example>=AREAS((A2:D7,B5:D6,C4))</Example>
  </AREAS>
  <ASC>
    <Description>The ASC function changes the double-byte characters to single-byte characters for DBCS languages.</Description>
    <Syntax>ASC(text) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ASC("SYNCFUSION")</Example>
  </ASC>
  <ASECH>
    <Description>The ASECH function computes the inverse hyperbolic secant for each element of y.</Description>
    <Syntax>ASECH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ASECH(0)</Example>
  </ASECH>
  <ASIN>
    <Description>Returns the inverse sine of a number. Inverse sine is also referred to as arcsine.The returned angle is given in radians in the range from -pi/2 to +pi/2.</Description>
    <Syntax>ASIN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ASIN(1)</Example>
  </ASIN>
  <ASINH>
    <Description>Returns the inverse hyperbolic sine of a number. The inverse hyperbolic sine is the value whose hyperbolic sine is the given number.</Description>
    <Syntax>ASINH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ASINH(1)</Example>
  </ASINH>
  <ATAN>
    <Description>Returns the inverse tangent of a number.The returned angle is given in radians in the range from -pi/2 to +pi/2.</Description>
    <Syntax>ATAN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ATAN(1)</Example>
  </ATAN>
  <ATAN2>
    <Description>Returns the inverse tangent of the specified x and y co-ordinates. The angle is given in radians between -pi and pi,excluding -pi.</Description>
    <Syntax>ATAN2(x_num,y_num)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ATAN2(1,2)</Example>
  </ATAN2>
  <ATANH>
    <Description>Returns the inverse hyperbolic tangent of a number. The inverse hyperbolic tangent is the value whose hyperbolic tangent is number,so ATANH(TANH(number)) equals the given number.</Description>
    <Syntax>ATANH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ATANH(0.76159416)</Example>
  </ATANH>
  <AVEDEV>
    <Description>Returns the average of the absolute mean deviations of data points. AVEDEV is a measure of the variability in a data set.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVEDEV(number1, number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVEDEV(1,2,3,4)</Example>
  </AVEDEV>
  <AVERAGE>
    <Description>Returns the average (arithmetic mean) of the arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVERAGE(number1, number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVERAGE(A2:A8)</Example>
  </AVERAGE>
  <AVERAGEA>
    <Description>Calculates the average (arithmetic mean) of the values in the list of arguments. In addition to numbers and text  logical values such as True and False are also included in the calculation.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVERAGEA(value1, value2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVERAGEA(A2:A6)</Example>
  </AVERAGEA>
  <AVERAGEIF>
    <Description>The AVERAGEIF function finds the average of values in a given array that satisfy a given criteria,and returns the average value of the corresponding values in a second given array.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVERAGEIF(range, criteria, average_range)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVERAGEIF(B2:B8,">70")</Example>
  </AVERAGEIF>
  <AVERAGEIFS>
    <Description>The AVERAGEIFS function finds the average of values in a given array that satisfy a set of given criteria.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVERAGEIFS(average_range, criteria_range1, criteria1, [criteria_range2, criteria2],... )</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVERAGEIFS(C2:C5,B2:B5,">7")</Example>
  </AVERAGEIFS>
  <AVG>
    <Description>Returns the average (arithmetic mean) of the arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>AVG(number1, number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=AVG(1,2,3)</Example>
  </AVG>
  <BAHTTEXT>
    <Description>The BAHTTEXT function converts a number into Thai text,with the the suffix "Baht". </Description>
    <Syntax>BAHTTEXT(num or reference cell) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BAHTTEXT(A2)</Example>
  </BAHTTEXT>
  <BASE>
    <Description>Converts a number into a text representation with the given radix (base).</Description>
    <Syntax>BASE(Number, Radix[Min_length])</Syntax>
    <Example>=BASE(7,2)</Example>
  </BASE>
  <BESSELI>
    <Description>The BESSELI function calculates the modified Bessel functions. These functions are the equivalent of the Bessel functions,evaluated for purely imaginary arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>BESSELI(a, n)</Syntax>
    <Example>=BESSELI(1.5,2)</Example>
  </BESSELI>
  <BESSELJ>
    <Description>The BESSELJ function calculates the Bessel function,Jn(x),for a specified order and a given value of x.</Description>
    <Syntax>BESSELJ(a, n) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BESSELJ(1.5,2)</Example>
  </BESSELJ>
  <BESSELK>
    <Description>The BESSELK function retrieves the modified Bessel function K n(x),which is equivalent to the Bessel functions evaluated for purely imaginary arguments. </Description>
    <Syntax>BESSELK(x, n) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BESSELK(1.5,2)</Example>
  </BESSELK>
  <BESSELY>
    <Description>The BESSELY function calculates for a specified order and value of x.</Description>
    <Syntax>BESSELY(a, n) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BESSELY(1.5,2)</Example>
  </BESSELY>
  <BETA.DIST>
    <Description>The beta distribution is commonly used to study variation in the percentage of something across samples,such as the fraction of the day people spend watching television.</Description>
    <Syntax>BETA.DIST(x, alpha, beta, cumulative, [A], [B])</Syntax>
    <Example>=BETA.DIST(A8,A3,A4,TRUE,A5,A6)</Example>
  </BETA.DIST>
  <BIGMUL>
    <Description>The BIGMUL function gives the full value of multiplying two 32-bit numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>BIGMUL(x, y); </Syntax>
    <Example>=BIGMUL(12534, 10)</Example>
  </BIGMUL>
  <BIN2DEC>
    <Description>The BIN2DEC function converts a binary number into a decimal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>BIN2DEC(num) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BIN2DEC(100100100)</Example>
  </BIN2DEC>
  <BIN2HEX>
    <Description>The BIN2HEX function converts a binary number into a hexadecimal.</Description>
    <Syntax>BIN2HEX(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BIN2HEX(1100,5)</Example>
  </BIN2HEX>
  <BIN2OCT>
    <Description>The BIN2OCT function converts a binary number into an octal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>BIN2OCT(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BIN2OCT(100100100)</Example>
  </BIN2OCT>
  <BINOM.DIST>
    <Description>The BINOM.DIST function returns the Binomial Distribution probability for a given number of successes from a specified number of trials. </Description>
    <Syntax>BINOM.DIST (trial number, sp, value, cumulative) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BINOM.DIST(A1,B9,G8,E2)</Example>
  </BINOM.DIST>
  <BINOM.INV>
    <Description>The BINOM.INV function returns the smallest value for which the cumulative binomial distribution is greater than or equal to a criterion value.</Description>
    <Syntax>BINOM.INV(trial number, sp, value) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BINOM.INV(10,0.4,0.7)</Example>
  </BINOM.INV>
  <BINOMDIST>
    <Description>Returns the individual term binomial distribution probability. </Description>
    <Syntax>BINOMDIST(number_s, trials, probability_s, cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=BINOMDIST(A1,B9,G8,E2)</Example>
  </BINOMDIST>
  <BITAND>
    <Description>The BITAND function returns a bitwise 'AND' of two numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>BITAND(num1, num2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=BITAND(12,5)</Example>
  </BITAND>
  <BITLSHIFT>
    <Description>The BITLSHIFT function retrieves a number shifted left by the specified number of bits.</Description>
    <Syntax>BITLSHIFT(num1, num2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=BITLSHIFT(12,5)</Example>
  </BITLSHIFT>
  <BITOR>
    <Description>The BITOR function retrieves a bitwise 'OR' of two numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>BITOR(num1, num2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BITOR(12,5)</Example>
  </BITOR>
  <BITRSHIFT>
    <Description>The BITRSHIFT function retrieves a number shifted right by the specified number of bits.</Description>
    <Syntax>BITRSHIFT(num1, num2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=BITRSHIFT(122,2)</Example>
  </BITRSHIFT>
  <BITXOR>
    <Description>The BITXOR function retrieves a bitwise 'XOR' of two numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>BITXOR(num1, num2b)</Syntax>
    <Example>=BITXOR(12,5)</Example>
  </BITXOR>
  <CEILING>
    <Description>Returns number rounded up,away from zero,to the nearest multiple of significance. For example,if you want to avoid using pennies in your prices and your product is priced at $4.82,use the formula =CEILING(4.82,0.05) to round prices up to the nearest nickel.</Description>
    <Syntax>CEILING(number, significance)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CEILING(2.5,1)</Example>
  </CEILING>
  <CEILING.MATH>
    <Description>The CEILING.MATH function returns number rounded up to a multiple of another number.</Description>
    <Syntax>CEILING.MATH(number, [significance], [mode]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CEILING.MATH(3.5,1)</Example>
  </CEILING.MATH>
  <CELL>
    <Description>The CELL function returns information about a given cell. This can be information in relation to the contents,formatting,or location of the cell. </Description>
    <Syntax>CELL(infoType, reference)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CELL("CONTENTS",A2)</Example>
  </CELL>
  <CHAR>
    <Description>The Char function returns the character whose number code is defined in the parameter.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHAR(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CHAR(66)</Example>
  </CHAR>
  <CHIDIST>
    <Description>The CHIDIST function calculates the right-tailed probability of the chi-square distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHIDIST(x, degFreedom) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHIDIST(25,12)</Example>
  </CHIDIST>
  <CHIINV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the one-tailed probability of the chi-squared (χ2) distribution. If probability = CHIDIST(x,...),then CHIINV(probability,...) = x. Use this function to compare observed results with expected ones in order to decide whether your original hypothesis is valid.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHIINV(probability, degrees_freedom)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CHIINV(A2,A3)</Example>
  </CHIINV>
  <CHISQ.DIST>
    <Description>The CHISQ.DIST function calculates the Probability Density Function or the Cumulative Distribution Function for the chi-square distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHISQ.DIST(x, degFreedom, cumulative) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHISQ.DIST(E4,E5,FALSE)</Example>
  </CHISQ.DIST>
  <CHISQ.DIST.RT>
    <Description>The CHISQ.DIST.RT function calculates the right-tailed probability of the chi-square distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHISQ.DIST.RT(x, degFreedom) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHISQ.DIST.RT(12,4)</Example>
  </CHISQ.DIST.RT>
  <CHISQ.INV>
    <Description>The CHISQ.INV function returns the inverse of the left-tailed probability of the chi-squared distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHISQ.INV(probability, degFreedom) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHISQ.INV(0.5,2)</Example>
  </CHISQ.INV>
  <CHISQ.INV.RT>
    <Description>The CHISQ.INV.RT function calculates the inverse of the right-tailed probability of the chi-square distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHISQ.INV.RT(probability, degFreedom) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHISQ.INV.RT(0.5,5)</Example>
  </CHISQ.INV.RT>
  <CHISQ.TEST>
    <Description>The CHISQ.TEST function function performs the chi-square test on two supplied data sets (of observed and expected frequencies),and returns the probability that the differences between the sets are simply due to sampling error. </Description>
    <Syntax>CHISQ.TEST(O_range, E_range) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CHISQ.TEST(A3:B4,A6:B7)</Example>
  </CHISQ.TEST>
  <CHITEST>
    <Description>Returns the test for independence. CHITEST returns the value from the chi-squared (c2) distribution for the statistic and the appropriate degrees of freedom. </Description>
    <Syntax>CHITEST(actual_range, expected_range)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CHITEST(A3:B5,A6:B8)</Example>
  </CHITEST>
  <CHOOSE>
    <Description>The Choose function returns the value from a range of values on a specific index.</Description>
    <Syntax>CHOOSE(index, valuearray)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CHOOSE(2,A2,A3,A4,A5)</Example>
  </CHOOSE>
  <CLEAN>
    <Description>The CLEAN function is used to remove the non-printable characters from the given text,represented by numbers 0 to 31 of the 7-bit ASCII code.</Description>
    <Syntax>CLEAN(Text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CLEAN("Syncfusion")</Example>
  </CLEAN>
  <CODE>
    <Description>The CODE function converts the first character of a supplied text string into numeric character set code.</Description>
    <Syntax>CODE(name) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CODE("S")</Example>
  </CODE>
  <COLUMN>
    <Description>The Column function returns the column index of the provided column in range. </Description>
    <Syntax>COLUMN(range)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COLUMN(B6)</Example>
  </COLUMN>
  <COLUMNS>
    <Description>The COLUMNS function returns the number of columns that are contained within the range. </Description>
    <Syntax>COLUMNS(array) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COLUMNS(B2:D4)</Example>
  </COLUMNS>
  <COMBIN>
    <Description>Returns the number of combinations for a given number of items. Use COMBIN to determine the total possible number of groups for a given number of items.</Description>
    <Syntax>COMBIN(number, number_chosen)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COMBIN(8,2)</Example>
  </COMBIN>
  <COMBINA>
    <Description>For a given number of items,the COMBINA function returns the number of combinations.</Description>
    <Syntax>COMBINA(number1, number2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COMBINA(2,5)</Example>
  </COMBINA>
  <COMPLEX>
    <Description>The COMPLEX function converts real and imaginary coefficients into a complex number of the form a + bi  or a + bj. </Description>
    <Syntax>COMPLEX(num, inum, suffix) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COMPLEX(1,2)</Example>
  </COMPLEX>
  <CONCATENATE>
    <Description>Joins several text strings into one text string.</Description>
    <Syntax>CONCATENATE (text1, text2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CONCATENATE(E9, " ", B10)</Example>
  </CONCATENATE>
  <CONFIDENCE>
    <Description>Returns a value that you can use to construct a confidence interval about a population mean. The confidence interval is a range of values. In your sample,mean x is at the center of this range and the range is x ± CONFIDENCE. For example,if x is the sample mean of delivery times for products ordered through the mail,x ± CONFIDENCE is a range of population means. </Description>
    <Syntax>CONFIDENCE(alpha, standard_dev, size)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CONFIDENCE(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </CONFIDENCE>
  <CONFIDENCE.NORM>
    <Description>The CONFIDENCE.NORM function uses a Normal Distribution to calculate a confidence value that can be used to construct the confidence interval for a population mean,for a supplied probability and sample size.</Description>
    <Syntax>CONFIDENCE.NORM(alpha, stdev, size) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CONFIDENCE.NORM(A8,A6,C2)</Example>
  </CONFIDENCE.NORM>
  <CONFIDENCE.T>
    <Description>CONFIDENCE.T function retrieves the confidence interval for a population mean.</Description>
    <Syntax>CONFIDENCE.T(alpha, stdev, size) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CONFIDENCE.T(3%,1,90)</Example>
  </CONFIDENCE.T>
  <CONVERT>
    <Description>Converts a number from one measurement system to another. For example,CONVERT can translate a table of distances in miles to a table of distances in kilometers.</Description>
    <Syntax>CONVERT(number, from_unit, to_unit)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CONVERT(1,"lbm","kg")</Example>
  </CONVERT>
  <CORREL>
    <Description>Returns the correlation coefficient of the array1 and array2 cell ranges. </Description>
    <Syntax>CORREL(array1, array2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CORREL(A2:A6,B2:B6)</Example>
  </CORREL>
  <COS>
    <Description>Returns the cosine of the given angle.</Description>
    <Syntax>COS(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COS(1)</Example>
  </COS>
  <COSH>
    <Description>Returns the hyperbolic cosine of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>COSH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COSH(1)</Example>
  </COSH>
  <COT>
    <Description>The COT function returns the cotangent of an angle specified in radians.</Description>
    <Syntax>COT(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COT(60)</Example>
  </COT>
  <COTH>
    <Description>The COTH function returns the hyperbolic cotangent of a hyperbolic angle.</Description>
    <Syntax>COTH(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COTH(60)</Example>
  </COTH>
  <COUNT>
    <Description>Counts the number of items in a list that contains numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>COUNT(value1, value2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COUNT(E2:E6)</Example>
  </COUNT>
  <COUNTA>
    <Description>Counts the number of cells that are not empty.</Description>
    <Syntax>COUNTA(value1, value2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COUNTA(E2:E6)</Example>
  </COUNTA>
  <COUNTBLANK>
    <Description>Counts empty cells in a specified range of cells.</Description>
    <Syntax>COUNTBLANK(range)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COUNTBLANK(A1:G10)</Example>
  </COUNTBLANK>
  <COUNTIF>
    <Description>Counts the number of cells within a range that meet the given criteria.</Description>
    <Syntax>COUNTIF(range, criteria)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COUNTIF(A2:A5,">0.5")</Example>
  </COUNTIF>
  <COVAR>
    <Description>Returns covariance,the average of the products of deviations for each data point pair. </Description>
    <Syntax>COVAR(array1, array2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=COVAR(A2:A6,B2:B6)</Example>
  </COVAR>
  <COVARIANCE.P>
    <Description>The COVARIANCE.P function retrieves population covariance,the average of the products of deviations for each data point pair in two data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>COVARIANCE.P(array1, array2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COVARIANCE.P(C1:C8,D1:D8)</Example>
  </COVARIANCE.P>
  <COVARIANCE.S>
    <Description>The COVARIANCE.S function returns the sample covariance,the average of the products of deviations for each data point pair in two data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>COVARIANCE.S(array1, array2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=COVARIANCE.S(C1:C8,D1:D8)</Example>
  </COVARIANCE.S>
  <CRITBINOM>
    <Description>Returns the smallest value for which,the cumulative binomial distribution is greater than or equal to a criterion value.</Description>
    <Syntax>CRITBINOM(trials, probability_s, alpha)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CRITBINOM(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </CRITBINOM>
  <CSC>
    <Description>The CSC function returns the cosecant of an angle specified in radians.</Description>
    <Syntax>CSC(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CSC(45)</Example>
  </CSC>
  <CSCH>
    <Description>The CSCH function returns the hyperbolic cosecant of an angle specified in radians.</Description>
    <Syntax>CSCH(number</Syntax>
    <Example>=CSCH(45)</Example>
  </CSCH>
  <CUMIPMT>
    <Description>Returns the cumulative interest paid on a loan between start_period and end_period.</Description>
    <Syntax>CUMIPMT(rate, nper, pv, start_period, end_period, type)</Syntax>
    <Example>=CUMIPMT(A2/12,A3*12,A4,13,24,0)</Example>
  </CUMIPMT>
  <CUMPRINC>
    <Description>The CUMPRINC function calculates the cumulative payment on the principal of a loan or investment,between two specified periods. </Description>
    <Syntax>CUMPRINC(rate, np, pv, startPeriod, endPeriod, pp) </Syntax>
    <Example>=CUMPRINC(A8/12,A9*12,G5,13,24,0)</Example>
  </CUMPRINC>
  <DATE>
    <Description>Returns the sequential serial number that represents a particular date. </Description>
    <Syntax>DATE(year, month, day)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DATE(A2,B2,C2)</Example>
  </DATE>
  <DATEVALUE>
    <Description>Returns the serial number of the date represented by the date_text.</Description>
    <Syntax>DATEVALUE(date_text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DATEVALUE("8/22/2011")</Example>
  </DATEVALUE>
  <DAVERAGE>
    <Description>The DAVERAGE function finds the average values obtained from a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DAVERAGE(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DAVERAGE(A4:E10,3,A4:E10)</Example>
  </DAVERAGE>
  <DAY>
    <Description>Returns the day of a date,represented by a serial number. The day is given as an integer ranging from 1 to 31.DAY(serial_number)</Description>
    <Syntax>DAY(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DAY(A2)</Example>
  </DAY>
  <DAYS>
    <Description>Returns the number of days between two dates.</Description>
    <Syntax>DAYS(end_date, start_date)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DAYS("3/15/11","2/1/11")</Example>
  </DAYS>
  <DAYS360>
    <Description>Returns the number of days between two dates based on a 360-day year (twelve 30-day months) which,is used in some accounting calculations. </Description>
    <Syntax>DAYS360(start_date, end_date, method)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DAYS360(G2,G6)</Example>
  </DAYS360>
  <DB>
    <Description>Returns the depreciation of an asset for a specified period using the fixed-declining balance method.</Description>
    <Syntax>DB(cost, salvage, life, period, month)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DB(A2,A3,A4,1,7)</Example>
  </DB>
  <DCOUNT>
    <Description>The DCOUNT function counts the number of cells that contain numbers in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DCOUNT(collection, column, condition)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DCOUNT(A4:E10,"Age",A1:F2)</Example>
  </DCOUNT>
  <DCOUNTA>
    <Description>The DCOUNTA function counts the number of nonblank cells in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DCOUNTA(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DCOUNTA(A4:E10,"Height",A1:F3)</Example>
  </DCOUNTA>
  <DDB>
    <Description>Returns the depreciation of an asset for a specified period using the double-declining balance method or some other method you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>DDB(cost, salvage, life, period, factor)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DDB(A2,A3,A4*365,1)</Example>
  </DDB>
  <DEC2BIN>
    <Description>The DEC2BIN function converts a decimal number into a binary number.</Description>
    <Syntax>DEC2BIN(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DEC2BIN(2,5)</Example>
  </DEC2BIN>
  <DEC2HEX>
    <Description>The DEC2HEX function converts a decimal number into hexadecimal number. </Description>
    <Syntax>DEC2HEX(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DEC2HEX(12)</Example>
  </DEC2HEX>
  <DEC2OCT>
    <Description>The DEC2OCT function converts a decimal number into an octal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>DEC2OCT(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DEC2OCT(124,3)</Example>
  </DEC2OCT>
  <DECIMAL>
    <Description>A text representation of a number in a given base has been converted into a decimal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>DECIMAL(text,radix</Syntax>
    <Example>=DECIMAL("AB",16)</Example>
  </DECIMAL>
  <DEGREES>
    <Description>Converts radians into degrees.</Description>
    <Syntax>DEGREES(angle)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DEGREES(PI())</Example>
  </DEGREES>
  <DELTA>
    <Description>The DELTA function tests two numbers for equality and returns the Kronecker Delta. Returns 1 if a =b; returns 0 otherwise.</Description>
    <Syntax>DELTA(num1, num2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DELTA(5,5)</Example>
  </DELTA>
  <DEVSQ>
    <Description>Returns the sum of squares of deviations of data points from their sample mean.</Description>
    <Syntax>DEVSQ(number1, number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DEVSQ(A2:A8)</Example>
  </DEVSQ>
  <DGET>
    <Description>The DGET function renders value from the column of list from the specified condition.</Description>
    <Syntax>DGET(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DGET(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:F2)</Example>
  </DGET>
  <DISC>
    <Description>The DISC function returns security discount rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>DISC(SettlementDate, MaturityDate, rate, value) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DISC("1/25/2007","6/15/2007",C4,B8)</Example>
  </DISC>
  <DIVREM>
    <Description>The DIVREM function calculates the quotient of two numbers and also returns the remainder in an output parameter.</Description>
    <Syntax>DIVREM(num1, num2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DIVREM(135234,12)</Example>
  </DIVREM>
  <DMAX>
    <Description>The DMAX function returns the largest number in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DMAX(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DMAX(A4:E10,"Profit",A1:A3)</Example>
  </DMAX>
  <DMIN>
    <Description>The DMIN function returns the smallest number in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DMIN(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DMIN(A4:E10,"Profit",A1:B2)</Example>
  </DMIN>
  <DOLLAR>
    <Description>The Dollar function converts a number to text,using a currency format. The format used is $#,##0.00_);($#,##0.00).</Description>
    <Syntax>DOLLAR (number, decimal_places)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DOLLAR(A2,2)</Example>
  </DOLLAR>
  <DOLLARDE>
    <Description>A dollar price expressed as a fraction converts into a dollar price expressed as a decimal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>DOLLARDE( arg1, arg2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DOLLARDE(B1,B2)</Example>
  </DOLLARDE>
  <DOLLARFR>
    <Description>A dollar price expressed as a decimal number converts into a dollar price expressed as a fraction.</Description>
    <Syntax>DOLLARFR (decNum, arg2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DOLLARFR(C1,C2)</Example>
  </DOLLARFR>
  <DPRODUCT>
    <Description>The DPRODUCT function estimates the product of a population based on a sample by using the numbers in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DPRODUCT(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DPRODUCT(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:B2)</Example>
  </DPRODUCT>
  <DSTDEV>
    <Description>The DSTDEV function estimates the standard deviation of a population based on a sample by using the numbers in a column of a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DSTDEV(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DSTDEV(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:A3)</Example>
  </DSTDEV>
  <DSTDEVP>
    <Description>The DSTDEVP function calculates the standard deviation of a population based on the entire population,using the numbers in a column of a list that match the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DSTDEVP(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DSTDEVP(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:A3)</Example>
  </DSTDEVP>
  <DSUM>
    <Description>The DSUM function adds the numbers in a field (column) of records in a list that matches the given conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DSUM(collection, column, condition)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DSUM(A4:E10,"Profit",A1:F2)</Example>
  </DSUM>
  <DURATION>
    <Description>Returns the annual duration of a security with periodic interest payments.</Description>
    <Syntax>DURATION(SettlementDate, MaturityDate, rate, profit, frequency, basis)</Syntax>
    <Example>=DURATION(C1,C2,C3,C4,C5,C6)</Example>
  </DURATION>
  <DVAR>
    <Description>The DVAR function estimates the variance of a population based on a sample by using the numbers in a column of a list which matches the conditions. </Description>
    <Syntax> VAR(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>==DVAR(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:A3)</Example>
  </DVAR>
  <DVARP>
    <Description>The DVARP function calculates the variance of a population based on the entire population by using the numbers in a column of a list or database that matches the conditions.</Description>
    <Syntax>DVARP(collection, column, condition) </Syntax>
    <Example>=DVARP(A4:E10,"Yield",A1:A3)</Example>
  </DVARP>
    <EDATE>
    <Description>The EDATE function returns a date that is a specified number of months before or after a supplied start date.</Description>
    <Syntax>EDATE( startDate, Months )</Syntax>
    <Example>=EDATE(A2,1)</Example>
  </EDATE>
  <EOMONTH>
    <Description>The EOMONTH function returns the last day of the month that is a specified number of months before or after an initially supplied start date.  </Description>
    <Syntax>EOMONTH(startDate, Months) </Syntax>
    <Example>=EOMONTH(A2,1)</Example>
  </EOMONTH>
  <ENCODEURL>
    <Description>The ENCODEURL function retrieves a URL-encoded string.</Description>
    <Syntax>ENCODEURL(name) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ENCODEURL("syncfusion worldwide")</Example>
  </ENCODEURL>
  <ERF>
    <Description>The ERF function calculates the Error Function,integrated between two supplied limits. </Description>
    <Syntax>ERF(lowerLimit, upperLimit) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ERF(1)</Example>
  </ERF>
  <ERF.PRECISE>
    <Description>The ERF.PRECISE function calculates the Error Function,integrated between a supplied lower or upper limit and 0.</Description>
    <Syntax>ERF.PRECISE(a) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ERF.PRECISE(2) </Example>
  </ERF.PRECISE>
<ERFC>
    <Description>The ERFC function calculates the complementary Error Function.</Description>
    <Syntax>ERFC(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ERFC(1)</Example>
  </ERFC>
  <ERFC.PRECISE>
    <Description>The ERFC.PRECISE function calculates the complementary Error Function,integrated between a supplied lower or upper limit and 0.</Description>
    <Syntax>ERFC.PRECISE(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ERFC.PRECISE(0.44)</Example>
  </ERFC.PRECISE>
  <ERROR.TYPE>
    <Description>Returns a number corresponding to one of the error values in Microsoft Excel or returns the #N/A error if no error exists. You can use ERROR.TYPE in an IF function to test for an error value and return a text string,such as a message,instead of the error value.</Description>
    <Syntax>ERROR.TYPE(error_val)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ERROR.TYPE(G9)</Example>
  </ERROR.TYPE>
  <EVEN>
    <Description>Returns number rounded up to the nearest even integer. You can use this function for processing items that come in twos. For example,a packing crate accepts rows of one or two items. The crate is full when the number of items,rounded up to the nearest two,matches the crate's capacity.</Description>
    <Syntax>EVEN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=EVEN(1.5)</Example>
  </EVEN>
  <EXACT>
    <Description>Compares two text strings and returns TRUE if they are exactly the same,FALSE otherwise. EXACT is case-sensitive but ignores formatting differences. Use EXACT to test text being entered into a document.</Description>
    <Syntax>EXACT(text1, text2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=EXACT(A2,B2)</Example>
  </EXACT>
  <EXP>
    <Description>Returns e raised to the power of number. The constant e equals 2.71828182845904,the base of the natural logarithm.</Description>
    <Syntax>EXP(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=EXP(1)</Example>
  </EXP>
  <EXPON.DIST>
    <Description>The EXPON.DIST function calculates the value of the probability density function or the cumulative distribution function for the exponential distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>EXPON.DIST(x, y, cumulative) </Syntax>
    <Example>=EXPON.DIST(A2,A3,TRUE)</Example>
  </EXPON.DIST>
  <EXPONDIST>
    <Description>Returns the exponential distribution. </Description>
    <Syntax>EXPONDIST(x, lambda, cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=EXPONDIST(B2,B3,TRUE)</Example>
  </EXPONDIST>
  <F.DIST>
    <Description>The F.DIST function calculates the Probability Density Function or the Cumulative Distribution Function for the F Distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>F.DIST(x, degFreedom1, degFreedom2, cumulative) </Syntax>
    <Example>=F.DIST(12,4,3,TRUE)</Example>
  </F.DIST>
  <F.DIST.RT>
    <Description>The F.DIST.RT function calculates the F Probability Distribution,which measures the degree of diversity between two data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>F.DIST.RT(x, degFreedom1, degFreedom2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=F.DIST.RT(12,4,3)</Example>
  </F.DIST.RT>
  <F.INV.RT>
    <Description>The F.INV.RT function calculates the inverse of the Cumulative F Distribution for a supplied probability.</Description>
    <Syntax>F.INV.RT(probability, degFreedom1, degFreedom2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=F.INV.RT(0.4,6,4)</Example>
  </F.INV.RT>
  <FACT>
    <Description>Returns the factorial of a number. The factorial of a number is equal to 1*2*3*...* number.</Description>
    <Syntax>FACT(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FACT(5)</Example>
  </FACT>
  <FACTDOUBLE>
    <Description>Returns the double factorial of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>FACTDOUBLE(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FACTDOUBLE(6)</Example>
  </FACTDOUBLE>
  <FALSE>
    <Description>Returns the logical value FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>FALSE()</Syntax>
    <Example>=FALSE()</Example>
  </FALSE>
  <FDIST>
    <Description>Returns the (right-tailed) F probability distribution (degree of diversity) for two data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>FDIST(x, deg_freedom1, deg_freedom2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FDIST(15.2068,6,4)</Example>
  </FDIST>
  <FILTERXML>
    <Description>Returns specific data from the XML content by using the specified xpath.</Description>
    <Syntax>FILTERXML(xml, xpath)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FILTERXML(WEBSERVICE(G10),"//rc/@title")</Example>
  </FILTERXML>
  <FIND>
    <Description>FIND and FINDB locate one text string within a second text string,and return the number of the starting position of the first text string from the first character of the second text string. </Description>
    <Syntax>FIND(find_text, within_text, [start_num])</Syntax>
    <Example>=FIND("m","Mathematics",2)</Example>
  </FIND>
  <FINDB>
    <Description>The FINDB function finds one text string (text1) within another text string (text2) and returns the number of the starting position of text1,based on the number of bytes each character uses,from the first character of text2. </Description>
    <Syntax>FINDB(text1, text2, num) </Syntax>
    <Example>=FINDB("a","Mathematics",2)</Example>
  </FINDB>
  <FINV>
    <Description>The F distribution can be used in an F-test that compares the degree of variability in two data sets</Description>
    <Syntax>FINV(probability, deg_freedom1, deg_freedom2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FINV(0.4,6,4)</Example>
  </FINV>
  <FISHER>
    <Description>Returns the Fisher transformation at x. This transformation produces a function that is normally distributed rather than skewed. Use this function to perform hypothesis testing on the correlation coefficient.</Description>
    <Syntax>FISHER(x)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FISHER(0.75)</Example>
  </FISHER>
  <FISHERINV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the Fisher transformation. Use this transformation when analyzing correlations between ranges or arrays of data. If y = FISHER(x),then FISHERINV(y) = x.</Description>
    <Syntax>FISHERINV(y)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FISHERINV(0.972955)</Example>
  </FISHERINV>
  <FIXED>
    <Description>Rounds a number to the specified number of decimals,formats the number in decimal format using a period and commas,and returns the result as text.</Description>
    <Syntax>FIXED(number, [decimals], [no_commas])</Syntax>
    <Example>=FIXED(A2,-1)</Example>
  </FIXED>
  <FLOOR>
    <Description>Rounds number down,toward zero,to the nearest multiple of significance.</Description>
    <Syntax>FLOOR(number, significance)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FLOOR(3.7,2)</Example>
  </FLOOR>
  <FORECAST>
    <Description>Calculates,or predicts,a future value by using existing values. The predicted value is a y-value for a given x-value. The known values are existing x-values and y-values,and the new value is predicted by using linear regression. You can use this function to predict future sales,inventory requirements,or consumer trends.</Description>
    <Syntax>FORECAST(x, known_y's, known_x's)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FORECAST(30,A2:A6,B2:B6)</Example>
  </FORECAST>
  <FORMULATEXT>
    <Description>Returns a formula as a string.</Description>
    <Syntax>FORMULATEXT(reference)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FORMULATEXT(A2)</Example>
  </FORMULATEXT>
  <FV>
    <Description>Returns the future value of an investment based on periodic,constant payments and a constant interest rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>FV(rate, nper, pmt, [pv], [type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=FV(A2/12,A3,A4,A5,A6)</Example>
  </FV>
  <FVSCHEDULE>
    <Description>Returns the future value of an initial principal after applying a series of compound interest rates. Use FVSCHEDULE to calculate the future value of an investment with a variable or adjustable rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>FVSCHEDULE(principal, schedule)</Syntax>
    <Example>=FVSCHEDULE(1,{0.09,0.11,0.1})</Example>
  </FVSCHEDULE>
  <GAMMA.DIST>
    <Description>Returns the gamma distribution. You can use this function to study variables that may have a skewed distribution. The gamma distribution is commonly used in queuing analysis.</Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMA.DIST(x, alpha, beta, cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMA.DIST(G7,A3,A8,FALSE)</Example>
  </GAMMA.DIST>
  <GAMMA.INV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the gamma cumulative distribution. If p = GAMMA.DIST(x,...),then GAMMA.INV(p,...) = x. </Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMA.INV(probability, alpha, beta)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMA.INV(D8,D3,D10)</Example>
  </GAMMA.INV>
  <GAMMADIST>
    <Description>Returns the gamma distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMADIST(x, alpha, beta, cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMADIST(G7,A3,A8:A8,FALSE)</Example>
  </GAMMADIST>
  <GAMMAINV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the gamma cumulative distribution. If p = GAMMADIST(x,...),then GAMMAINV(p,...) = x.</Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMAINV(probability, alpha, beta)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMAINV(G7,D3,A5)</Example>
  </GAMMAINV>
  <GAMMALN>
    <Description>Returns the natural logarithm of the gamma function,Γ(x).</Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMALN(x)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMALN(4)</Example>
  </GAMMALN>
  <GAMMALN.PRECISE>
    <Description>Returns the natural logarithm of the gamma function,Γ(x).</Description>
    <Syntax>GAMMALN.PRECISE(x)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GAMMALN.PRECISE(10)</Example>
  </GAMMALN.PRECISE>
  <GCD>
    <Description>Returns the greatest common divisor of two or more integers. The greatest common divisor is the largest integer that divides both number1 and number2 without a remainder.</Description>
    <Syntax>GCD(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GCD(5,2)</Example>
  </GCD>
  <GEOMEAN>
    <Description>Returns the geometric mean of an array or range of positive data. For example,you can use GEOMEAN to calculate average growth rate given compound interest with variable rates.</Description>
    <Syntax>GEOMEAN(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=GEOMEAN(A2:A8)</Example>
  </GEOMEAN>
  <GESTEP>
    <Description>Returns 1 if number ≥ step; returns 0 (zero) otherwise. Use this function to filter a set of values</Description>
    <Syntax>GESTEP(number,[step])</Syntax>
    <Example>=GESTEP(5,5)</Example>
  </GESTEP>
  <GROWTH>
    <Description>Calculates predicted exponential growth by using existing data. GROWTH returns the y-values for a series of new x-values that you specify by using existing x-values and y-values. You can also use the GROWTH worksheet function to fit an exponential curve to existing x-values and y-values.</Description>
    <Syntax>GROWTH(known_y's,[known_x's],[new_x's],[const])</Syntax>
    <Example>=GROWTH(B2:B7,C2:C7)</Example>
  </GROWTH>
  <HARMEAN>
    <Description>Returns the harmonic mean of a data set. The harmonic mean is the reciprocal of the arithmetic mean of reciprocals.</Description>
    <Syntax>HARMEAN(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=HARMEAN(A2:A8)</Example>
  </HARMEAN>
  <HEX2BIN>
    <Description>Converts a hexadecimal number to binary.</Description>
    <Syntax>HEX2BIN(number,[places])</Syntax>
    <Example>=HEX2BIN("F",8)</Example>
  </HEX2BIN>
  <HEX2DEC>
    <Description>Converts a hexadecimal number to decimal.</Description>
    <Syntax>HEX2DEC(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=HEX2DEC("AA")</Example>
  </HEX2DEC>
  <HEX2OCT>
    <Description>Converts a hexadecimal number to octal.</Description>
    <Syntax>HEX2OCT(number, [places])</Syntax>
    <Example>=HEX2OCT("F1",3)</Example>
  </HEX2OCT>
  <HLOOKUP>
    <Description>Searches for a value in the top row of a table or an array (array: Used to build single formulas that produce multiple results or that operate on a group of arguments that are arranged in rows and columns. An array range shares a common formula; an array constant is a group of constants used as an argument.) of values,and then returns a value in the same column from a row you specify in the table or array. Use HLOOKUP when your comparison values are located in a row across the top of a table of data,and you want to look down a specified number of rows. Use VLOOKUP when your comparison values are located in a column to the left of the data you want to find.</Description>
    <Syntax>HLOOKUP(lookup_value, table_array, row_index_num, [range_lookup])</Syntax>
    <Example>=HLOOKUP(6,A1:B4,2,TRUE)</Example>
  </HLOOKUP>
  <HOUR>
    <Description>Returns the hour of a time value. The hour is given as an integer,ranging from 0 (12:00 A.M.) to 23 (11:00 P.M.).</Description>
    <Syntax>HOUR(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=HOUR(A4)</Example>
  </HOUR>
  <HYPERLINK>
    <Description>Creates a shortcut or jump that opens a document stored on a network server,an intranet (intranet: A network within an organization that uses Internet technologies (such as the HTTP or FTP protocol). By using hyperlinks,you can explore objects,documents,pages,and other destinations on the intranet.),or the Internet. When you click the cell that contains the HYPERLINK function,Microsoft Excel opens the file that is stored at link_location.</Description>
    <Syntax>HYPERLINK(link_location,[friendly_name])</Syntax>
    <Example>=HYPERLINK("http://www.syncfusion.com","Click this")</Example>
  </HYPERLINK>
  <HYPGEOM.DIST>
    <Description>Returns the hypergeometric distribution. HYPGEOM.DIST returns the probability of a given number of sample successes,given the sample size,population successes,and population size.</Description>
    <Syntax>HYPGEOM.DIST(sample_s,number_sample,population_s,number_pop,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=HYPGEOM.DIST(F2,D2,E4,A9,TRUE)</Example>
  </HYPGEOM.DIST>
  <HYPGEOMDIST>
    <Description>Returns the hypergeometric distribution. HYPGEOMDIST returns the probability of a given number of sample successes,given the sample size,population successes,and population size.</Description>
    <Syntax>HYPGEOMDIST(sample_s,number_sample,population_s,number_pop)</Syntax>
    <Example>=HYPGEOMDIST(A1,A2,A9,A7)</Example>
  </HYPGEOMDIST>
  <IEEEREMAINDER>
    <Description>IEEERemainder function returns the remainder operation on two arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>IEEERemainder(d1,d2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IEEEREMAINDER(12534,10)</Example>
  </IEEEREMAINDER>
  <IF>
    <Description>The IF function returns one value if a condition you specify evaluates to TRUE,and another value if that condition evaluates to FALSE. </Description>
    <Syntax>IF(logical_test,[value_if_true],[value_if_false])</Syntax>
    <Example>=IF(A2=100,"Within budget","Over budget")</Example>
  </IF>
  <IFERROR>
    <Description>Returns a value you specify if a formula evaluates to an error; otherwise,returns the result of the formula. </Description>
    <Syntax>IFERROR(value,value_if_error)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IFERROR(A2/B2,"Error in calculation")</Example>
  </IFERROR>
  <IFNA>
    <Description>Returns the value you specify if the formula returns the #N/A error value; otherwise returns the result of the formula.</Description>
    <Syntax>IFNA(value,value_if_na)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IFNA(VLOOKUP("125000",A5:B10,2),"Not found")</Example>
  </IFNA>
  <IHDIST>
    <Description>Returns the results from the sum on n independent standard uniform variables.</Description>
    <Syntax>IHDIST(number1, number2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IHDIST(1,3)</Example>
  </IHDIST>
  <IMABS>
    <Description>Returns the absolute value (modulus) of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMABS(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMABS("5+12i")</Example>
  </IMABS>
  <IMAGINARY>
    <Description>Returns the IMAGINARY coefficient of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMAGINARY(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMAGINARY("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMAGINARY>
  <IMARGUMENT>
    <Description>Returns the argument Theta (theta),an angle expressed in radians</Description>
    <Syntax>IMARGUMENT(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMARGUMENT("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMARGUMENT>
  <IMCONJUGATE>
    <Description>Returns the complex conjugate of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCONJUGATE(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCONJUGATE("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMCONJUGATE>
  <IMCOS>
    <Description>Returns the cosine of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCOS(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCOS("1+i")</Example>
  </IMCOS>
  <IMCOSH>
    <Description>Returns the hyperbolic cosine of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCOSH(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCOSH("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMCOSH>
  <IMCOT>
    <Description>Returns the cotangent of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCOT(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCOT("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMCOT>
  <IMCOTH>
    <Description>The IMCOTH function calculates the hyperbolic cotangent of the complex number z. </Description>
    <Syntax>IMCOTH(inum) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCOTH("1+2i")</Example>
  </IMCOTH>
  <IMCSC>
    <Description>The IMCSC function retrieves the cosecant of a complex number in a+bi or a+bj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCSC(inum)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCSC("1+2i")</Example>
  </IMCSC>
  <IMCSCH>
    <Description>The IMCSCH function calculates the hyperbolic cosecant of a complex number in a + bi or a + bj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMCSCH(inum) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IMCSCH("1+2i")</Example>
  </IMCSCH>
  <IMDIV>
    <Description>The IMDIV function calculates the quotient of two complex numbers in a + bi  or a + bj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMDIV(inum1, inum2) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IMDIV("1+2i","1+2i")</Example>
  </IMDIV>
  <IMEXP>
    <Description>The IMEXP function calculates the exponential of a complex number z.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMEXP(inum) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IMEXP("1+2i")</Example>
  </IMEXP>
  <IMLN>
    <Description>Returns the natural logarithm of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMLN(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMLN("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMLN>
  <IMLOG10>
    <Description>Returns the common logarithm (base 10) of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMLOG10(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMLOG10("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMLOG10>
  <IMLOG2>
    <Description>Returns the base-2 logarithm of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMLOG2(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMLOG2("3+4i")</Example>
  </IMLOG2>
  <IMPOWER>
    <Description>Returns a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format raised to a power.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMPOWER(inumber, number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMPOWER("2+3i",3)</Example>
  </IMPOWER>
  <IMPRODUCT>
    <Description>Returns the product of 1 to 255 complex numbers in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMPRODUCT(inumber1, [inumber2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMPRODUCT("3+4i","5-3i")</Example>
  </IMPRODUCT>
  <IMREAL>
    <Description>Returns the real coefficient of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMREAL(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMREAL("6-9i")</Example>
  </IMREAL>
  <IMSEC>
    <Description>Returns the secant of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSEC(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSEC("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMSEC>
  <IMSECH>
    <Description>Returns the hyperbolic secant of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSECH(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSECH("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMSECH>
  <IMSIN>
    <Description>Returns the sine of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSIN(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSIN("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMSIN>
  <IMSINH>
    <Description>Returns the hyperbolic sine of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSINH(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSINH("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMSINH>
  <IMSQRT>
    <Description>Returns the square root of a complex number in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSQRT(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSQRT("1+i")</Example>
  </IMSQRT>
  <IMSUB>
    <Description>Returns the difference of two complex numbers in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSUB(inumber1,inumber2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSUB("12+4i","5+3i")</Example>
  </IMSUB>
  <IMSUM>
    <Description>Returns the sum of two or more complex numbers in x + yi or x + yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMSUM(inumber1, [inumber2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMSUM("3+4i","5-3i")</Example>
  </IMSUM>
  <IMTAN>
    <Description>Returns the tangent of a complex number in x+yi or x+yj text format.</Description>
    <Syntax>IMTAN(inumber)</Syntax>
    <Example>=IMTAN("4+3i")</Example>
  </IMTAN>
  <IMTANH>
    <Description>The IMTANH function calculates the hyperbolic tangent of the complex number z. </Description>
    <Syntax>IMTANH(inum) </Syntax>
    <Example>=IMTANH("1+2i")</Example>
  </IMTANH>
  <INDEX>
    <Description>Returns a value or the reference to a value from within a table or range. There are two forms of the INDEX function: the array (array: Used to build single formulas that produce multiple results or that operate on a group of arguments that are arranged in rows and columns. An array range shares a common formula; an array constant is a group of constants used as an argument.) form and the reference form.</Description>
    <Syntax>INDEX(array, row_num, [column_num])</Syntax>
    <Example>=INDEX(A2:C6,2,3)</Example>
  </INDEX>
  <INDIRECT>
    <Description>Returns the reference specified by a text string. References are immediately evaluated to display their contents.</Description>
    <Syntax>INDIRECT(ref_text, [a1])</Syntax>
    <Example>=INDIRECT(A3)</Example>
  </INDIRECT>
  <INFO>
    <Description>Returns information about the current operating environment.</Description>
    <Syntax>INFO(type_text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=INFO("RELEASE")</Example>
  </INFO>
  <INT>
    <Description>Rounds a number down to the nearest integer.</Description>
    <Syntax>INT(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=INT(8.9)</Example>
  </INT>
  <INTERCEPT>
    <Description>Calculates the point at which a line will intersect the y-axis by using existing x-values and y-values. The intercept point is based on a best-fit regression line plotted through the known x-values and known y-values. Use the INTERCEPT function when you want to determine the value of the dependent variable when the independent variable is 0 (zero).</Description>
    <Syntax>INTERCEPT(known_y's,known_x's)</Syntax>
    <Example>=INTERCEPT(A2:A6,B2:B6)</Example>
  </INTERCEPT>
  <INTRATE>
    <Description>Returns the interest rate for a fully invested security.</Description>
    <Syntax>INTRATE(settlement,maturity,investment,redemption,[basis])</Syntax>
    <Example>=INTRATE("2/15/2008","5/15/2008",B7,G3)</Example>
  </INTRATE>
  <IPMT>
    <Description>Returns the interest payment for a given period for an investment based on periodic,constant payments and a constant interest rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>IPMT(rate,per,nper,pv,[fv],[type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=IPMT(A2/12,A3,A4*12,A5)</Example>
  </IPMT>
  <IRR>
    <Description>Returns the internal rate of return for a series of cash flows represented by the numbers in values. These cash flows do not have to be even,as they would be for an annuity. However,the cash flows must occur at regular intervals,such as monthly or annually. The internal rate of return is the interest rate received for an investment consisting of payments (negative values) and income (positive values) that occur at regular periods.</Description>
    <Syntax>IRR(values,[guess])</Syntax>
    <Example>=IRR(G1:G6)</Example>
  </IRR>
  <ISBLANK>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISBLANK(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISBLANK(C2)</Example>
  </ISBLANK>
  <ISERR>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISERR(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISERR(A6/0)</Example>
  </ISERR>
  <ISERROR>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISERROR(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISERROR(A4)</Example>
  </ISERROR>
  <ISEVEN>
    <Description>Returns TRUE if number is even,or FALSE if number is odd.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISEVEN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISEVEN(-2)</Example>
  </ISEVEN>
  <ISFORMULA>
    <Description>Checks whether there is a reference to a cell that contains a formula,and returns TRUE or FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISFORMULA(reference)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISFORMULA(A1)</Example>
  </ISFORMULA>
  <ISLOGICAL>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISLOGICAL(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISLOGICAL(TRUE)</Example>
  </ISLOGICAL>
  <ISNA>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISNA(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISNA(A4)</Example>
  </ISNA>
  <ISNONTEXT>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISNONTEXT(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISNONTEXT(2)</Example>
  </ISNONTEXT>
  <ISNUMBER>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISNUMBER(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISNUMBER(E3)</Example>
  </ISNUMBER>
  <ISODD>
    <Description>Returns TRUE if number is odd,or FALSE if number is even.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISODD(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISODD(-1)</Example>
  </ISODD>
  <ISOWEEKNUM>
    <Description>Returns number of the ISO week number of the year for a given date.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISOWEEKNUM(date)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISOWEEKNUM(A2)</Example>
  </ISOWEEKNUM>
  <ISPMT>
    <Description>Calculates the interest paid during a specific period of an investment. This function is provided for compatibility with Lotus 1-2-3.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISPMT(rate, per, nper, pv)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISPMT(A2/12,A3,A4*12,A5)</Example>
  </ISPMT>
  <ISREF>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISREF(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISREF("XYZ1")</Example>
  </ISREF>
  <ISTEXT>
    <Description>Each of these functions,referred to collectively as the IS functions,checks the specified value and returns TRUE or FALSE depending on the outcome. For example,the ISBLANK function returns the logical value TRUE if the value argument is a reference to an empty cell; otherwise it returns FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>ISTEXT(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ISTEXT(E2)</Example>
  </ISTEXT>
  <JIS>
    <Description>The JIS function changes single-byte English letters or katakana within a character string to double-byte characters. This function is a Japanese-specific feature.</Description>
    <Syntax>JIS(name) </Syntax>
    <Example>=JIS("syncfusion")</Example>
  </JIS>
  <KURT>
    <Description>Returns the kurtosis of a data set. Kurtosis characterizes the relative peakedness or flatness of a distribution compared with the normal distribution. Positive kurtosis indicates a relatively peaked distribution. Negative kurtosis indicates a relatively flat distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>KURT(number1, [number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=KURT(A2:A9)</Example>
  </KURT>
  <LARGE>
    <Description>Returns the k-th largest value in a data set. You can use this function to select a value based on its relative standing. For example,you can use LARGE to return the highest,runner-up,or third-place score.</Description>
    <Syntax>LARGE(array, k)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LARGE(A2:B6,3)</Example>
  </LARGE>
  <LCM>
    <Description>Returns the least common multiple of integers. The least common multiple is the smallest positive integer that is a multiple of all integer arguments number1,number2,and so on. Use LCM to add fractions with different denominators.</Description>
    <Syntax>LCM(number1, [number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LCM(A2,B3,A7)</Example>
  </LCM>
  <LEFT>
    <Description>LEFT returns the first character or characters in a text string,based on the number of characters you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>LEFT(text, [num_chars])</Syntax>
    <Example>=LEFT(A4,4)</Example>
  </LEFT>
  <LEFTB>
    <Description>LEFTB returns the first character or characters in a text string,based on the number of bytes you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>LEFTB(text, [num_bytes])</Syntax>
    <Example>=LEFTB(B2,4)</Example>
  </LEFTB>
  <LEN>
    <Description>LEN returns the number of characters in a text string.</Description>
    <Syntax>LEN(text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LEN(A2)</Example>
  </LEN>
  <LENB>
    <Description>LENB returns the number of bytes used to represent the characters in a text string. </Description>
    <Syntax>LENB(text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LENB(A6)</Example>
  </LENB>
  <LN>
    <Description>Returns the natural logarithm of a number. Natural logarithms are based on the constant e (2.71828182845904).</Description>
    <Syntax>LN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LN(86)</Example>
  </LN>
  <LOG>
    <Description>Returns the logarithm of a number to the base you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOG(number, [base])</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOG(10)</Example>
  </LOG>
  <LOG10>
    <Description>Returns the base-10 logarithm of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOG10(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOG10(86)</Example>
  </LOG10>
  <LOGEST>
    <Description>In regression analysis,calculates an exponential curve that fits your data and returns an array of values that describes the curve.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGEST(known_y's,[known_x's],[const],[stats])</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGEST(B2:B7,A2:A7)</Example>
  </LOGEST>
  <LOGESTB>
    <Description>In regression analysis,calculates an exponential curve that fits your data and returns an array of values that describes the curve.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGESTB(known_y's,[known_x's],[const],[stats])</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGESTB(B2:B7,A2:A7)</Example>
  </LOGESTB>
  <LOGINV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the lognormal cumulative distribution function of x,where ln(x) is normally distributed with parameters mean and standard_dev. If p = LOGNORMDIST(x,...) then LOGINV(p,...) = x.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGINV(probability,mean,standard_dev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGINV(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </LOGINV>
  <LOGNORM.DIST>
    <Description>Returns the lognormal distribution of x,where ln(x) is normally distributed with parameters Mean and Standard_dev.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGNORM.DIST(x,mean,standard_dev,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGNORM.DIST(A2,A3,A4,TRUE)</Example>
  </LOGNORM.DIST>
  <LOGNORM.INV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the lognormal cumulative distribution function of x,where ln(x) is normally distributed with parameters Mean and Standard_dev. If p = LOGNORM.DIST(x,...) then LOGNORM.INV(p,...) = x.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGNORM.INV(probability,mean,standard_dev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGNORM.INV(A4,A5,A6)</Example>
  </LOGNORM.INV>
  <LOGNORMDIST>
    <Description>Returns the cumulative lognormal distribution of x,where ln(x) is normally distributed with parameters mean and standard_dev. Use this function to analyze data that has been logarithmically transformed.

</Description>
    <Syntax>LOGNORMDIST(x, mean, standard_dev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOGNORMDIST(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </LOGNORMDIST>
  <LOOKUP>
    <Description>The LOOKUP function returns a value either from a one-row or one-column range (range: Two or more cells on a sheet. The cells in a range can be adjacent or nonadjacent.) or from an array (array: Used to build single formulas that produce multiple results or that operate on a group of arguments that are arranged in rows and columns. An array range shares a common formula; an array constant is a group of constants used as an argument.). The LOOKUP function has two syntax forms: the vector form and the array form.</Description>
    <Syntax>ARRAY FORM :-  LOOKUP(lookup_value, array)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOOKUP(10,{10,60,70,80,90},{"f","d","c","b","a"})</Example>
  </LOOKUP>
  <LOWER>
    <Description>Converts all uppercase letters in a text string to lowercase.</Description>
    <Syntax>LOWER(text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=LOWER(A2)</Example>
  </LOWER>
  <MATCH>
    <Description>The MATCH function searches for a specified item in a range (range: Two or more cells on a sheet. The cells in a range can be adjacent or nonadjacent.) of cells,and then returns the relative position of that item in the range.</Description>
    <Syntax>MATCH(lookup_value, lookup_array, [match_type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=MATCH(39,B2:B5,1)</Example>
  </MATCH>
  <MAX>
    <Description>Returns the largest value in a set of values.</Description>
    <Syntax>MAX(number1, [number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MAX(A2:A6)</Example>
  </MAX>
  <MAXA>
    <Description>Returns the largest value in a list of arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>MAXA(value1, [value2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MAXA(E2:E3)</Example>
  </MAXA>
  <MDETERM>
    <Description>Returns the matrix determinant of an array.</Description>
    <Syntax>MDETERM(array)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MDETERM(A2:D5)</Example>
  </MDETERM>
  <MEDIAN>
    <Description>Returns the median of the given numbers. The median is the number in the middle of a set of numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>MEDIAN(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MEDIAN(A2:A7)</Example>
  </MEDIAN>
  <MID>
    <Description>MID returns a specific number of characters from a text string,starting at the position you specify,based on the number of characters you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>MID(text,start_num,num_chars)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MID(E9,1,5)</Example>
  </MID>
  <MIDB>
    <Description>MIDB returns a specific number of characters from a text string,starting at the position you specify,based on the number of bytes you specify. </Description>
    <Syntax>MIDB(text,start_num,num_bytes)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MIDB(E9,1,7)</Example>
  </MIDB>
  <MIN>
    <Description>Returns the smallest number in a set of values.</Description>
    <Syntax>MIN(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MIN(A2:A6)</Example>
  </MIN>
  <MINA>
    <Description>Returns the smallest value in the list of arguments. </Description>
    <Syntax>MINA(value1,[value2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MINA(E2:E3)</Example>
  </MINA>
  <MINUTE>
    <Description>Returns the minutes of a time value. The minute is given as an integer,ranging from 0 to 59.</Description>
    <Syntax>MINUTE(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MINUTE(E1)</Example>
  </MINUTE>
  <MINVERSE>
    <Description>Returns the inverse matrix for the matrix stored in an array.</Description>
    <Syntax>MINVERSE(array)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MINVERSE(A1:B2)</Example>
  </MINVERSE>
  <MIRR>
    <Description>Returns the modified internal rate of return for a series of periodic cash flows. MIRR considers both the cost of the investment and the interest received on reinvestment of cash.</Description>
    <Syntax>MIRR(values,finance_rate,reinvest_rate)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MIRR(G1:G6,G7,G8)</Example>
  </MIRR>
  <MMULT>
    <Description>Returns the matrix product of two arrays. The result is an array with the same number of rows as array1 and the same number of columns as array2.</Description>
    <Syntax>MMULT(array1,array2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MMULT(A1:B2,A5:B6)</Example>
  </MMULT>
  <MOD>
    <Description>Returns the remainder after number is divided by divisor. The result has the same sign as divisor.</Description>
    <Syntax>MOD(number,divisor)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MOD(3,2)</Example>
  </MOD>
  <MODE>
    <Description>Returns the most frequently occurring,or repetitive,value in an array or range of data.</Description>
    <Syntax>MODE(number1,[number2],...])</Syntax>
    <Example>=MODE(E4:E7)</Example>
  </MODE>
  <MODE.MULT>
    <Description>Returns a vertical array of the most frequently occurring,or repetitive values in an array or range of data. For horizontal arrays,use TRANSPOSE(MODE.MULT(number1,number2,...)).</Description>
    <Syntax>MODE.MULT((number1,[number2],...])</Syntax>
    <Example>=MODE.MULT(A2:E2)</Example>
  </MODE.MULT>
  <MODE.SNGL>
    <Description>Returns the most frequently occurring,or repetitive,value in an array or range of data. </Description>
    <Syntax>MODE.SNGL(number1,[number2],...])</Syntax>
    <Example>=MODE.SNGL(E4:E7)</Example>
  </MODE.SNGL>
  <MONTH>
    <Description>Returns the MONTH of a date represented by a serial number. The month is given as an integer,ranging from 1 (January) to 12 (December).</Description>
    <Syntax>MONTH(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MONTH(E1)</Example>
  </MONTH>
  <MROUND>
    <Description>Returns a number rounded to the desired multiple.</Description>
    <Syntax>MROUND(number, multiple)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MROUND(10,3)</Example>
  </MROUND>
  <MULTINOMIAL>
    <Description>Returns the ratio of the factorial of a sum of values to the product of factorials.</Description>
    <Syntax>MULTINOMIAL(number1, [number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MULTINOMIAL(2,3,4)</Example>
  </MULTINOMIAL>
  <MUNIT>
    <Description>Returns the unit matrix for the specified dimension.</Description>
    <Syntax>MUNIT(dimension)</Syntax>
    <Example>=MUNIT(3)</Example>
  </MUNIT>
    <N>
    <Description>The N function converts the given value into a numeric value.</Description>
    <Syntax>=N(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=N(FALSE)</Example>
  </N>
  <NA>
    <Description>The NA function returns the #N/A error. This error message is produced when a formula is unable to find a value that it needs. This error message denotes 'value not available.'</Description>
    <Syntax>=NA()</Syntax>
    <Example>=NA()</Example>
  </NA>
  <NETWORKDAYS>
    <Description>The NETWORKDAYS function is used to calculate the number of whole work days between two given dates. This includes all weekdays from Monday to Friday,but excludes a supplied list of holidays.</Description>
    <Syntax>= NETWORKDAYS( start_date,end_date,[holidays] )</Syntax>
    <Example>=NETWORKDAYS(DATE(2012,10,1),DATE(2013,3,1))</Example>
  </NETWORKDAYS>
  <NETWORKDAYS.INTL>
    <Description>NETWORKDAYS.INTL calculates the number of whole work days between two supplied dates.</Description>
    <Syntax>=NETWORKDAYS.INTL(startDate,endDate)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NETWORKDAYS.INTL("1/10/2012","1/3/2013")</Example>
  </NETWORKDAYS.INTL>
  <NORM.DIST>
    <Description>The NORM.DIST function calculates the normal distribution for a supplied value of x,and a supplied distribution mean &amp; standard deviation.</Description>
    <Syntax>=NORM.DIST(x,mean,stdev,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORM.DIST(C4,C5,C6,TRUE)</Example>
  </NORM.DIST>
  <NORM.INV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the normal cumulative distribution for the specified mean and standard deviation.</Description>
    <Syntax>NORMINV(probability,mean,stdev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORMINV(F5,F6,F7)</Example>
  </NORM.INV>
  <NORM.S.DIST>
    <Description>The NORM.S.DIST function returns the standard normal distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>NORM.S.DIST(val,cumulative).</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORM.S.DIST(C4,TRUE)</Example>
  </NORM.S.DIST>
  <NORM.S.INV>
    <Description>The NORM.S.INV function returns the inverse of the standard normal cumulative distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>NORM.S.INV(probability) </Syntax>
    <Example>=NORM.S.INV(0.75)</Example>
  </NORM.S.INV>
  <NORMDIST>
    <Description>Returns the normal distribution for the specified mean and standard deviation.</Description>
    <Syntax>NORMDIST(x,mean,standard_dev,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORMDIST(C4,C5,C6,TRUE)</Example>
  </NORMDIST>
  <NORMINV>
    <Description>Returns the inverse of the normal cumulative distribution for the specified mean and standard deviation.</Description>
    <Syntax>NORMINV(probability,mean,stdev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORM.INV(F5,F6,F7)</Example>
  </NORMINV>
  <NORMSDIST>
    <Description>The NormsDist function returns the probability that the observed value of a standard normal random variable will be less than or equal to the parameter.

 </Description>
    <Syntax>NORMSDIST(value) where value is a numeric value that checks with the random variable</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORMSDIST(A5)</Example>
  </NORMSDIST>
  <NORMSINV>
    <Description>The NormsInv function returns the standard normal random variable that has Mean 0 and Standard Deviation 1</Description>
    <Syntax>NORMSINV(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NORMSINV(0.9088)</Example>
  </NORMSINV>
  <NOT>
    <Description>Reverses the value of its argument. Use NOT when you want to make sure a value is not equal to one particular value.</Description>
    <Syntax>NOT(logical)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NOT(B2+B4=5)</Example>
  </NOT>
  <NOW>
    <Description>Returns the serial number of the current date and time. If the cell format was General before the function was entered,Excel changes the cell format so that it matches the date and time format of your regional settings.</Description>
    <Syntax>=NOW()</Syntax>
    <Example>=NOW()</Example>
  </NOW>
  <NPER>
    <Description>Returns the number of periods for an investment based on periodic,constant payments and a constant interest rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>NPER(rate,pmt,pv,fv,type)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NPER(A5,B2,C5,C2,0)</Example>
  </NPER>
  <NPV>
    <Description>Calculates the net present value of an investment by using a discount rate and a series of future payments (negative values) and income (positive values).</Description>
    <Syntax>NPV(rate,value1,value2,...).</Syntax>
    <Example>=NPV(A2,A3,A4,A5,A6)</Example>
  </NPV>
  <NUMBERVALUE>
    <Description>The NUMBERVALUE function converts text to a number in a locale-independent way.</Description>
    <Syntax>NUMBERVALUE(text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NUMBERVALUE("3.5%")</Example>
  </NUMBERVALUE>
  <NEGBINOMDIST>
    <Description>Returns the negative binomial distribution. NEGBINOMDIST returns the probability that there will be number_f failures before the number_s-th success,when the constant probability of a success is probability_s. This function is similar to the binomial distribution,except that the number of successes is fixed,and the number of trials is variable. Like the binomial,trials are assumed to be independent.</Description>
    <Syntax>NEGBINOMDIST(number_f,number_s,probability_s)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NEGBINOMDIST(A2,B1,A4)</Example>
  </NEGBINOMDIST>
  <NEGBINOM.DIST>
    <Description>The NEGBINOM.DIST function calculates the probability mass function or the cumulative distribution function for the Negative Binomial Distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>NEGBINOM.DIST(F_number,S_number,S_probability,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=NEGBINOM.DIST(B1,B2,B3,FALSE)</Example>
  </NEGBINOM.DIST>
 <OCT2BIN>
    <Description>The OCT2BIN function converts an octal number into a binary number.</Description>
    <Syntax>OCT2BIN(num,places ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=OCT2BIN(124)</Example>
  </OCT2BIN>
  <OCT2DEC>
    <Description>The decimal value converts to an octal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>OCT2DEC(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=OCT2DEC(124)</Example>
  </OCT2DEC>
  <OCT2HEX>
    <Description>The OCT2HEX function converts an octal number into a hexadecimal number.</Description>
    <Syntax>OCT2HEX(num, [places]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=OCT2HEX(124)</Example>
  </OCT2HEX>
  <ODD>
    <Description>Returns the number rounded up to the nearest ODD integer.</Description>
    <Syntax>ODD(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ODD(1.5)</Example>
  </ODD>
  <OFFSET>
    <Description>The OFFSET function returns a reference to a range that is offset a number of rows and columns from any given range or cell.</Description>
    <Syntax>OFFSET( range, rows, columns, height, width )</Syntax>
    <Example>=OFFSET(D3,3,-2,1,1)</Example>
  </OFFSET>
  <OR>
    <Description>Returns TRUE if any argument is TRUE; returns FALSE if all arguments are FALSE.</Description>
    <Syntax>OR(logical1, [logical2], ...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=OR(TRUE)</Example>
  </OR>
  <PERCENTILE>
    <Description>Returns the k-th PERCENTILE of values in a range. You can use this function to establish a threshold of acceptance.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTILE(array, k)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTILE(A2:A5,0.3)</Example>
  </PERCENTILE>
  <PEARSON>
    <Description>Returns the PEARSON product moment correlation coefficient, r, a dimensionless index that ranges from -1.0 to 1.0 inclusive and reflects the extent of a linear relationship between two data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>PEARSON(array1, array2)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PEARSON(A3:A7,B3:B7)</Example>
  </PEARSON>
  <PERCENTILE.EXC>
    <Description>Returns the k-th PERCENTILE of values in a range, where k is in the range 0..1, exclusive.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTILE.EXC(array, k)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTILE.EXC(A2:A10, 0.25)</Example>
  </PERCENTILE.EXC>
  <PERCENTILE.INC>
    <Description>Returns the k-th percentile of values in a range, where k is in the range 0..1, inclusive.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTILE.INC(array, k)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTILE.INC(A2:A5,0.3)</Example>
  </PERCENTILE.INC>
  <PERCENTRANK>
    <Description>Returns the rank of a value in a data set as a percentage of the data set. This function can be used to evaluate the relative standing of a value within a data set.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTRANK(array, x, [significance])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTRANK(G1:G10,2)</Example>
  </PERCENTRANK>
  <PERCENTRANK.EXC>
    <Description>Returns the rank of a value in a data set as a percentage (0..1, exclusive) of the data set.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTRANK.EXC(array,x,[significance])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTRANK.EXC(G1:G7,2)</Example>
  </PERCENTRANK.EXC>
  <PERCENTRANK.INC>
    <Description>Returns the rank of a value in a data set as a percentage (0..1, inclusive) of the data set. This function can be used to evaluate the relative standing of a value within a data set.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERCENTRANK.INC(array, x, [significance])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERCENTRANK.INC(G1:G6,2)</Example>
  </PERCENTRANK.INC>
  <PERMUT>
    <Description>Returns the number of permutations for a given number of objects that can be selected from number objects. A permutation is any set or subset of objects or events where internal order is significant.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERMUT(number, number_chosen)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERMUT(B2,B3)</Example>
  </PERMUT>
  <PERMUTATIONA>
    <Description>Returns the number of permutations for a given number of objects (with repetitions) that can be selected from the total objects.</Description>
    <Syntax>PERMUTATIONA(number, number-chosen)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PERMUTATIONA(2,2)</Example>
  </PERMUTATIONA>
  <PI>
    <Description>Returns the number 3.14159265358979, the mathematical constant PI, accurate to 15 digits.</Description>
    <Syntax>PI()</Syntax>
    <Example>=PI()</Example>
  </PI>
  <PMT>
    <Description>Calculates the payment for a =SEARCH("base","database")loan based on constant payments and a constant interest rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>PMT(rate, nper, pv, [fv], [type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PMT(A2/12,A3,A4)</Example>
  </PMT>
  <POISSON>
    <Description>Returns the POISSON distribution. A common application of the Poisson distribution is predicting the number of events over a specific time, such as the number of cars arriving at a toll plaza in 1 minute.</Description>
    <Syntax>POISSON(x, mean, cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=POISSON(A2,A3,TRUE)</Example>
  </POISSON>
  <POISSON.DIST>
    <Description>Returns the Poisson distribution. A common application of the Poisson distribution is predicting the number of events over a specific time, such as the number of cars arriving at a toll plaza in 1 minute.</Description>
    <Syntax>POISSON.DIST(x, mean, cumulative)
</Syntax>
    <Example>=POISSON.DIST(B2,B3,TRUE)</Example>
  </POISSON.DIST>
  <POW>
    <Description>The POW function returns the number raised to the specified power.</Description>
    <Syntax>POW(number, power)</Syntax>
    <Example>=POW(5,2)</Example>
  </POW>
  <POWER>
    <Description>Returns the result of a number raised to a POWER.</Description>
    <Syntax>POWER(number, power)</Syntax>
    <Example>=POWER(100,2)</Example>
  </POWER>
  <PPMT>
    <Description>Returns the payment on the principal for a given period for an investment based on periodic, constant payments and a constant interest rate.</Description>
    <Syntax>PPMT(rate, per, nper, pv, [fv], [type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PPMT(A2/12, 1, A3*12, A4)</Example>
  </PPMT>
  <PROB>
    <Description>Returns the probability that values in a range are between two limits. If upper_limit is not supplied, returns the probability that values in x_range are equal to lower_limit.</Description>
    <Syntax>PROB(x_range, prob_range, [lower_limit], [upper_limit])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PROB(A3:A6,B3:B6,1,3)</Example>
  </PROB>
  <PRODUCT>
    <Description>The PRODUCT function multiplies all the numbers given as arguments and returns the product. </Description>
    <Syntax>PRODUCT(number1, [number2], ...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PRODUCT(A2:A4, 2)</Example>
  </PRODUCT>
  <PROPER>
    <Description>Capitalizes the first letter in a text string and any other letters in text that follow any character other than a letter. Converts all other letters to lowercase letters.</Description>
    <Syntax>PROPER(text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=PROPER(A2)</Example>
  </PROPER>
  <PV>
    <Description>Returns the present value of an investment. The present value is the total amount that a series of future payments is worth now</Description>
    <Syntax>PV(rate,nper,pmt,[fv],[type])</Syntax>
    <Example>=PV(500/12,12*A1,C2)</Example>
  </PV>
  <QUARTILE>
    <Description>Returns the QUARTILE of a data set. </Description>
    <Syntax>QUARTILE(array,quart)</Syntax>
    <Example>=QUARTILE(A2:A9,1)</Example>
  </QUARTILE>
  <QUARTILE.EXC>
    <Description>The QUARTILE.EXC function returns a requested quartile of a supplied range of values,based on a percentile range of 0 to 1 exclusive.</Description>
    <Syntax>QUARTILE.EXC(array,quart) </Syntax>
    <Example>=QUARTILE.EXC(B2:C7,3)</Example>
  </QUARTILE.EXC>
  <QUARTILE.INC>
    <Description>The QUARTILE.INC function returns a requested quartile of a supplied range of values,based on a percentile range of 0 to 1 inclusive.</Description>
    <Syntax>QUARTILE.INC(array,quart) </Syntax>
    <Example>=QUARTILE.INC(B1:B9,4)</Example>
  </QUARTILE.INC>
  <QUOTIENT>
    <Description>The QUOTIENT function returns the integer portion of a division between two given numbers. The returned value will be integer value.</Description>
    <Syntax>QUOTIENT (numerator,denominator)</Syntax>
    <Example>= QUOTIENT (10,3)</Example>
  </QUOTIENT>
  <RADIANS>
    <Description>Converts degrees to RADIANS.</Description>
    <Syntax>RADIANS(angle)</Syntax>
    <Example>=RADIANS(270)</Example>
  </RADIANS>
  <RAND>
    <Description>Returns an evenly distributed random number greater than or equal to 0 and less than 1.</Description>
    <Syntax>RAND( )</Syntax>
    <Example>=RAND()</Example>
  </RAND>
  <RANDBETWEEN>
    <Description>The RANDBETWEEN function returns a random number that is between the given ranges. This function returns a new random number each time in recalculation.</Description>
    <Syntax>RANDBETWEEN (start_num,end_num)</Syntax>
    <Example>= RANDBETWEEN (10,20)</Example>
  </RANDBETWEEN>
  <RANK>
    <Description>Returns the RANK of a number in a list of numbers. The rank of a number is its size relative to other values in a list. (If you were to sort the list,the rank of the number would be its position.)</Description>
    <Syntax>RANK(number,ref,order)</Syntax>
    <Example>=RANK(A3,A2:A6,1)</Example>
  </RANK>
    <RANK.EQ>
      <Description>The RANK.EQ function returns the statistical rank of a given value, within a supplied array of values</Description>
      <Syntax>RANK.EQ(number,ref,order)</Syntax>
      <Example>=RANK.EQ(A3,A2:A6,1)</Example>
    </RANK.EQ>
  <RANK.AVG>
    <Description>The RANK.AVG function returns the statistical rank of a given value,within a supplied array of values. If there are duplicate values in the list,the average rank is returned. </Description>
    <Syntax>RANK.AVG(number,ref) </Syntax>
    <Example>=RANK.AVG(14,B2:C7)</Example>
  </RANK.AVG>
  <RATE>
    <Description>Returns the interest rate per period of an annuity. RATE is calculated by iteration and may not converge to a unique solution. </Description>
    <Syntax>RATE(nper,pmt,pv,fv,type,guess)</Syntax>
    <Example>=RATE(A1*12,C10,F1)</Example>
  </RATE>
  <RECEIVED>
    <Description>The RECEIVED function returns the amount received at maturity for a fully invested security.</Description>
    <Syntax>RECEIVED(Settlementdate,MaturityDate,investment,discount,basis) </Syntax>
    <Example>=RECEIVED(G5,G2,10000000,5%)</Example>
  </RECEIVED>
  <REPLACE>
    <Description>The REPLACE function replaces a certain part of text with a different part of text based on the number of characters given.</Description>
    <Syntax>REPLACE(oldText,startNum,numChars,newText) </Syntax>
    <Example>=REPLACE(E9,6,5,"*")</Example>
  </REPLACE>
  <REPLACEB>
    <Description>The REPLACEB function replaces a certain part of text with a different part of text based on the number of bytes given.</Description>
    <Syntax>REPLACEB(oldText,startNum,numBytes,newText) </Syntax>
    <Example>=REPLACEB(F8,1,1,"@")</Example>
  </REPLACEB>
  <REPT>
    <Description>The REPT function returns a supplied text string,repeated a specified number of times.</Description>
    <Syntax>REPT(string,number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=REPT("*",7)</Example>
  </REPT>
  <RIGHT>
    <Description>RIGHT returns the last character or characters in a text string,based on the number of characters you specify.</Description>
    <Syntax>RIGHT(text,num_chars)</Syntax>
    <Example>=RIGHT(B2,5)</Example>
  </RIGHT>
  <RIGHTB>
    <Description>The RIGHTB function returns the last character or characters in a string,based on the number of bytes you specify for double-byte character set (DBCS) languages.</Description>
    <Syntax>RIGHTB(string,num) </Syntax>
    <Example>=RIGHTB(C2,6)</Example>
  </RIGHTB>
  <ROMAN>
    <Description>The ROMAN function converts an Arabic number to a Roman numeral. This function returns a text string depicting the Roman numeral form of the given number.</Description>
    <Syntax>ROMAN( number,(form) )</Syntax>
    <Example>= ROMAN(499,0)</Example>
  </ROMAN>
  <ROUND>
    <Description>Rounds a number to a specified number of digits.</Description>
    <Syntax>ROUND(number,num_digits)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ROUND(2.15,1)</Example>
  </ROUND>
  <ROUNDDOWN>
    <Description>Rounds a number down towards zero.</Description>
    <Syntax>ROUNDDOWN(number,num_digits)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ROUNDDOWN(3.2,0)</Example>
  </ROUNDDOWN>
  <ROUNDUP>
    <Description>Rounds a number up away from 0 (zero).</Description>
    <Syntax>ROUNDUP(number,num_digits)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ROUNDUP(3.2,0)</Example>
  </ROUNDUP>
  <ROW>
    <Description>The ROW function returns the first row number within a supplied reference,or if no reference is supplied,the function returns the number of the current row in the currently active spreadsheet.</Description>
    <Syntax>ROW( [reference] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ROW(B2)</Example>
  </ROW>
  <ROWS>
    <Description>The ROWS function takes a range and returns the number of rows that are contained within the range. </Description>
    <Syntax>ROWS( array ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=ROWS(B2:C4)</Example>
  </ROWS>
  <RRI>
    <Description>The RRI function returns an equivalent interest rate when investment value increases.</Description>
    <Syntax>RRI(np,pv,fv) </Syntax>
    <Example>=RRI(12,12000,15000)</Example>
  </RRI>
  <RSQ>
    <Description>Returns the square of the Pearson product moment correlation coefficient through data points in known_y's and known_x's. </Description>
    <Syntax>RSQ(known_y's,known_x's)</Syntax>
    <Example>=RSQ(A3:A9,B3:B9)</Example>
  </RSQ>
  <SEARCH>
    <Description>The SEARCH function returns the location of a substring in a string. This function is NOT case-sensitive.</Description>
    <Syntax>SEARCH(substring,string,[start_position] )</Syntax>
    <Example>=SEARCH("tab","database")  
</Example>
  </SEARCH>
  <SEARCHB>
    <Description>The SEARCHB function finds one text string (find_text) within another text string (within_text),and returns the number of the starting position of find_text for double-byte character set (DBCS) languages.</Description>
    <Syntax>SEARCHB(findText,withinText,startNum ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=SEARCHB("base","database")</Example>
  </SEARCHB>
  <SEC>
    <Description>The SEC function returns the secant of an angle.</Description>
    <Syntax>SEC(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SEC(B3)</Example>
  </SEC>
  <SECH>
    <Description>The SECH function returns the hyperbolic secant of an angle.</Description>
    <Syntax>SECH(number) </Syntax>
    <Example>=SECH(60)</Example>
  </SECH>
  <SECOND>
    <Description>Returns the seconds of a time value. The second is given as an integer in the range 0 (zero) to 59.</Description>
    <Syntax>SECOND(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SECOND(E1)</Example>
  </SECOND>
  <SERIESSUM>
    <Description>Returns the sum of a power series </Description>
    <Syntax>SERIESSUM(x, n, m, coefficients)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SERIESSUM(A3,0,2,A4:A7)</Example>
  </SERIESSUM>
  <SHEET>
    <Description>The SHEET function returns the sheet number of the reference sheet.</Description>
    <Syntax>SHEET([value]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=SHEET()</Example>
  </SHEET>
  <SHEETS>
    <Description>SHEETS function returns the number of sheets in a reference.</Description>
    <Syntax>SHEETS(reference) </Syntax>
    <Example>=SHEETS("A1")</Example>
  </SHEETS>
  <SIGN>
    <Description>Determines the SIGN of a number. Returns 1 if the number is positive,zero (0) if the number is 0 and -1 if the number is negative.</Description>
    <Syntax>SIGN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SIGN(1000)</Example>
  </SIGN>
  <SIN>
    <Description>Returns the SIN of the given angle.</Description>
    <Syntax>SIN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SIN(45)</Example>
  </SIN>
  <SINH>
    <Description>The SINH function computes the hyperbolic sine of the argument.</Description>
    <Syntax>SINH(value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SINH(1)</Example>
  </SINH>
  <SKEW>
    <Description>Returns the skewness of a distribution. Skewness characterizes the degree of asymmetry of a distribution around its mean. </Description>
    <Syntax>SKEW(number1, number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SKEW(A2:A9)</Example>
  </SKEW>
  <SKEW.P>
    <Description>Returns the skewness of a distribution based on a population: a characterization of the degree of asymmetry of a distribution around its mean.</Description>
    <Syntax>SKEW.P(number1, [number2],…) </Syntax>
    <Example>=SKEW.P(A2:A7)</Example>
  </SKEW.P>
  <SLN>
    <Description>Returns the straight-line depreciation of an asset for one period.</Description>
    <Syntax>SLN(cost, salvage, life)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SLN(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </SLN>
  <SLOPE>
    <Description>Returns the SLOPE of the linear regression line through data points in known_y's and known_x's. The slope is the rate of change along the regression line.</Description>
    <Syntax>SLOPE(known_y's, known_x's)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SLOPE(A3:A9,B3:B9)</Example>
  </SLOPE>
  <SMALL>
    <Description>Returns the k-th smallest value in a data set. </Description>
    <Syntax>SMALL(array, k)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SMALL(A2:A9,4)</Example>
  </SMALL>
  <SQRT>
    <Description>Returns a positive square root.</Description>
    <Syntax>SQRT(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SQRT(16)</Example>
  </SQRT>
  <SQRTPI>
    <Description>The SQRTPI function returns the square root of a given number multiplied by π. Here π is the constant math value.</Description>
    <Syntax>SQRTPI (number)</Syntax>
    <Example>= SQRTPI(2)</Example>
  </SQRTPI>
  <STANDARDIZE>
    <Description>Returns a normalized value from a distribution characterized by mean and standard_dev.</Description>
    <Syntax>STANDARDIZE(x,mean,standard_dev)</Syntax>
    <Example>=STANDARDIZE(A2,A3,A4)</Example>
  </STANDARDIZE>
  <STDEV>
    <Description>Estimates the standard deviation based on a sample. The standard deviation is a measure of how widely values are dispersed from the average value (the mean).</Description>
    <Syntax>STDEV(number1,number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEV(A3:A9)</Example>
  </STDEV>
  <STDEV.P>
    <Description>The STDEV.P function calculates the standard deviation of a supplied set of values.</Description>
    <Syntax>STDEV.P(number1,[number2],...])</Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEV.P(B1:B9)</Example>
  </STDEV.P>
  <STDEV.S>
    <Description>The STDEV.S function calculates the sample standard deviation of a supplied set of values.</Description>
    <Syntax>STDEV.S(number1,[number2],...]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEV.S(B1:B9)</Example>
  </STDEV.S>
  <STDEVA>
    <Description>Estimates standard deviation based on a sample. The standard deviation is a measure of how widely values are dispersed from the average value (the mean). Text and logical values such as True and False are also included in the calculation.</Description>
    <Syntax>STDEVA(value1,value2 ,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEVA(A3:A9)</Example>
  </STDEVA>
  <STDEVP>
    <Description>Calculates standard deviation based on the entire population given as arguments. </Description>
    <Syntax>STDEVP(number1,number2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEVP(A3:A9)</Example>
  </STDEVP>
  <STDEVPA>
    <Description>Calculates the standard deviation based on the entire population given as arguments,including text and logical values.</Description>
    <Syntax>STDEVPA(value1,value2,...)
</Syntax>
    <Example>=STDEVPA(A4:A10)</Example>
  </STDEVPA>
  <STEYX>
    <Description>Returns the standard error of the predicted y-value for each x in the regression. </Description>
    <Syntax>STEYX(known_y's,known_x's)</Syntax>
    <Example>=STEYX(A3:A9,B3:B9)</Example>
  </STEYX>
  <SUBSTITUTE>
    <Description>SUBSTITUTE new_text for old_text in a text string. Use SUBSTITUTE when you want to replace specific text in a text string; use REPLACE when you want to replace any text that occurs in a specific location in a text string.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUBSTITUTE(text,old_text,new_text,instance_num)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUBSTITUTE(A2,"Sales","Cost")</Example>
  </SUBSTITUTE>
  <SUBTOTAL>
    <Description>The SUBTOTAL function returns a subtotal in a list. Once the subtotal list is created,you can modify it by editing the SUBTOTAL function.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUBTOTAL(function_Number,ref1,(ref2),...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUBTOTAL(9,A2:A5)</Example>
  </SUBTOTAL>
  <SUM>
    <Description>The SUM function adds all numbers in a range of cells and returns the result.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUM( number1,number2,... number_n )</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUM(A1:A3,B2:C4,D5,D7)</Example>
  </SUM>
  <SUMIF>
    <Description>SUMIF function adds the specified range of cells by a given criteria.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMIF( range,criteria,sum_range )</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMIF(A2:A5,">0.5",B2:B5)</Example>
  </SUMIF>
  <SUMIFS>
    <Description>The SUMIFS function sums the values in a given array that satisfy a set of given criteria.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMIFS(sum_range,criteria_range1,criteria1,[criteria_range2,criteria2],…)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMIFS(C2:C5,B2:B5,">10")</Example>
  </SUMIFS>
  <SUMPRODUCT>
    <Description>Multiplies corresponding components in the given arrays and returns the sum of those products.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMPRODUCT(array1,array2,array3,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMPRODUCT(A2:B4,D2:E4)</Example>
  </SUMPRODUCT>
  <SUMSQ>
    <Description>Returns the sum of the squares of the arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMSQ(number1,number2,...)
</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMSQ(A2,A4)</Example>
  </SUMSQ>
  <SUMX2MY2>
    <Description>Returns the sum of the difference of squares of corresponding values in two arrays.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMX2MY2(array_x,array_y)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMX2MY2(A2:A8,B2:B8)</Example>
  </SUMX2MY2>
  <SUMX2PY2>
    <Description>Returns the sum of the sum of squares of corresponding values in two arrays. The sum of the sum of squares is a common term in many statistical calculations.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMX2PY2(array_x,array_y)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMX2PY2(A3:A9,B3:B9)</Example>
  </SUMX2PY2>
  <SUMXMY2>
    <Description>The SUMXMY2 function calculates the sum of the squares of the differences between the corresponding items in the arrays and returns the sum as results.</Description>
    <Syntax>SUMXMY2( array1,array2 )</Syntax>
    <Example>=SUMXMY2(A3:A9,B3:B9)</Example>
  </SUMXMY2>
  <SYD>
    <Description>Returns the sum-of-years' digits depreciation of an asset for a specified period.</Description>
    <Syntax>SYD(cost,salvage,life,per)</Syntax>
    <Example>=SYD(A2,A3,A4,1)</Example>
  </SYD>
  <T>
    <Description>The T function tests whether the given value is text or not. If the given value is text,then it returns the given text. Otherwise,the function returns an empty text string.</Description>
    <Syntax>T( value )</Syntax>
    <Example>=T("SYNCFUSION")</Example>
  </T>
  <T.DIST>
    <Description>Returns the Student's left-tailed t-distribution. The t-distribution is used in the hypothesis testing of small sample data sets.</Description>
    <Syntax>T.DIST(x,deg_freedom,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=T.DIST(60,1,TRUE)</Example>
  </T.DIST>
  <T.INV>
    <Description>Returns the left-tailed inverse of the Student's t-distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>T.INV(probability,deg_freedom)</Syntax>
    <Example>=T.INV(A5,B1)</Example>
  </T.INV>
  <TAN>
    <Description>Returns the tangent of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>TAN(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TAN(45)</Example>
  </TAN>
  <TANH>
    <Description>Returns the hyperbolic tangent of a number.</Description>
    <Syntax>TANH(number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TANH(-2)</Example>
  </TANH>
  <TEXT>
    <Description>Converts a value to text in a specific number format.</Description>
    <Syntax>TEXT(value, format_text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TEXT(C2,"$#,##0.00")</Example>
  </TEXT>
  <TIME>
    <Description>Returns the decimal number for a particular time.</Description>
    <Syntax>TIME(hour, minute, second)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TIME(A2,B2,C2)</Example>
  </TIME>
  <TIMEVALUE>
    <Description>Returns the decimal number of the time represented by a text string. The decimal number is a value ranging from 0 (zero) to 0.99999999,representing the times from 0:00:00 (12:00:00 A.M.) to 23:59:59 (11:59:59 P.M.).</Description>
    <Syntax>TIMEVALUE(time_text)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TIMEVALUE("22-Aug-2011 6:35 AM")</Example>
  </TIMEVALUE>
  <TODAY>
    <Description>Returns the serial number of the current date. The serial number is the number of days since Jan 1,1900.</Description>
    <Syntax>TODAY( )</Syntax>
    <Example>=TODAY()</Example>
  </TODAY>
  <TRANSPOSE>
    <Description>The TRANSPOSE function copies a horizontal range of cells into a vertical range and vice versa.</Description>
    <Syntax>TRANSPOSE( array ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=TRANSPOSE({10,20,30})</Example>
  </TRANSPOSE>
  <TRIM>
    <Description>The TRIM function returns a text value with the leading and trailing spaces removed.</Description>
    <Syntax>TRIM( text )</Syntax>
    <Example>=TRIM("First Quarter Earnings")</Example>
  </TRIM>
  <TRIMMEAN>
    <Description>Returns the mean of the interior of a data set. TRIMMEAN calculates the mean taken by excluding a percentage of data points from the top and bottom tails of a data set.</Description>
    <Syntax>TRIMMEAN(array,percent)</Syntax>
    <Example>=TRIMMEAN(A1:A9,1)</Example>
  </TRIMMEAN>
  <TRUE>
    <Description>The True function returns the logical value for  True.</Description>
    <Syntax>True()</Syntax>
    <Example>=TRUE()</Example>
  </TRUE>
  <TRUNC>
    <Description>The TRUNC function truncates a supplied number to a specified number of decimal places.</Description>
    <Syntax>TRUNC( number,[num_digits] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=TRUNC(1.25)</Example>
  </TRUNC>
  <TRUNCATE>
    <Description>The TRUNCATE function truncates a supplied number to a specified number of decimal places.</Description>
    <Syntax>TRUNCATE( number,[num_digits] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=TRUNCATE(1.25)</Example>
  </TRUNCATE>
  <TYPE>
    <Description>The TYPE function receives a value and returns an integer that represents the supplied value's data type. </Description>
    <Syntax>TYPE( value ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=TYPE(C4)</Example>
  </TYPE>
  <UNICHAR>
    <Description>The UNICHAR function retrieves the unicode character for a given numeric value.</Description>
    <Syntax>UNICHAR(num) </Syntax>
    <Example>=UNICHAR(100)</Example>
  </UNICHAR>
  <UNICODE>
    <Description>The UNICODE function calculates the number corresponding to the first character of the text.</Description>
    <Syntax>UNICODE(text) </Syntax>
    <Example>=UNICODE("d")</Example>
  </UNICODE>
  <UNIDIST>
    <Description>The UNIDIST function returns the PDF of the uniform distribution..</Description>
    <Syntax>UNIDIST(successes,trials,max)</Syntax>
    <Example>=UNIDIST(4,3,10)</Example>
  </UNIDIST>
  <UPPER>
    <Description>The UPPER function converts all characters in a text string to uppercase.</Description>
    <Syntax>UPPER( text )</Syntax>
    <Example>=UPPER(A2)</Example>
  </UPPER>
  <VALUE>
    <Description>The VALUE function computes the date or a string that contains the number,and converts it into number format.</Description>
    <Syntax>VALUE(range)</Syntax>
    <Example>=VALUE("E10")</Example>
  </VALUE>
  <VAR>
    <Description>The VAR function returns the variance of a population based on sample of numbers.</Description>
    <Syntax>VAR( number1,number2,... number_n )</Syntax>
    <Example>=VAR(A2:A9)</Example>
  </VAR>
  <VARA>
    <Description>The VARA function returns the variance of a population based on a sample of numbers,text,and logical values (ie: TRUE or FALSE). </Description>
    <Syntax>VARA( value1,value2,... value_n )</Syntax>
    <Example>=VARA(A4:A9)</Example>
  </VARA>
  <VARP>
    <Description>The VARP function returns population variance of the listed values.</Description>
    <Syntax>VARP(number1,[number2],...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=VARP(A2:A9)</Example>
  </VARP>
  <VARPA>
    <Description>Calculates variance based on the entire population. In addition to numbers and text,logical values such as True and False are also included in the calculation.</Description>
    <Syntax>VARPA(value1, value2,...)</Syntax>
    <Example>=VARPA(A4:A9)</Example>
  </VARPA>
  <VDB>
    <Description>Returns the depreciation of an asset for any period you specify,including partial periods,using the double-declining balance method or some other method you specify. VDB stands for variable declining balance.</Description>
    <Syntax>VDB(cost, salvage, life, start_period, end_period, factor, no_switch)</Syntax>
    <Example>=VDB(A2,A3,A4*365,0,1)</Example>
  </VDB>
  <VLOOKUP>
    <Description>Searches for a value in the left most column of a table and then returns a value in the same row from a column you specify in the table. Use VLOOKUP instead of HLOOKUP when your comparison values are located in a column to the left of the data you want to find.</Description>
    <Syntax>VLOOKUP(lookup_value, table_array, col_index_num, range_lookup)</Syntax>
    <Example>=VLOOKUP(1,A2:C9,2)</Example>
  </VLOOKUP>
  <WEBSERVICE>
    <Description>WEBSERVICE function retrieves data from a web service on the Internet.</Description>
    <Syntax>WEBSERVICE(url)</Syntax>
    <Example>=WEBSERVICE(G10)</Example>
  </WEBSERVICE>
  <WEEKDAY>
    <Description>Returns the day of the week corresponding to a date. The day is given as an integer,ranging from 1 (Sunday) to 7 (Saturday) by default.</Description>
    <Syntax>WEEKDAY(serial_number,return_type)</Syntax>
    <Example>=WEEKDAY(E1)</Example>
  </WEEKDAY>
  <WEEKNUM>
    <Description>For a supplied a date,the WEEKNUM function returns an integer representing the week number (from 1 to 53) of the year. </Description>
    <Syntax>WEEKNUM( serialNum,[returnType] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=WEEKNUM(E1,1)</Example>
  </WEEKNUM>
  <WEIBULL>
    <Description>The WEIBULL function  returns the Weibull distribution. This distribution is used in reliability analysis,such as calculating a device's mean time to failure.</Description>
    <Syntax>WEIBULL(x,alpha,beta,cumulative)</Syntax>
    <Example>=WEIBULL(A2,A3,A4,TRUE)</Example>
  </WEIBULL>
  <WEIBULL.DIST>
    <Description>The WEIBULL.DIST function returns the Weibull distribution.</Description>
    <Syntax>WEIBULL.DIST(x,alpha,beta,cumulative) </Syntax>
    <Example>=WEIBULL.DIST(B1,B2,B3,TRUE)</Example>
  </WEIBULL.DIST>
  <WORKDAY>
    <Description>The WORKDAY function returns a date that is a supplied number of working days (excluding weekends and holidays) ahead of a given start date. </Description>
    <Syntax>WORKDAY(startDate,Days,[holidays] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=WORKDAY(E1,E4)</Example>
  </WORKDAY>
  <WORKDAY.INTL>
    <Description>The WORKDAY.INTL function returns a date that is a supplied number of working days (excluding weekends and holidays) ahead of a given start date.</Description>
    <Syntax>WORKDAY.INTL( startDate,days,[weekend],[holidays] ) </Syntax>
    <Example>=WORKDAY.INTL(DATE(2014,1,1),100,1)</Example>
  </WORKDAY.INTL>
  <XIRR>
    <Description>The XIRR function computes the internal rate of return for a schedule of possibly non-periodic cash flows.</Description>
    <Syntax>XIRR(cashflow,datelist,value)</Syntax>
    <Example>=XIRR(F5:F7,F8:F10,0.1)</Example>
  </XIRR>
  <XOR>
    <Description>The XOR function returns the exclusive OR for the given arguments.</Description>
    <Syntax>XOR (logical_value1,logical_value2,…)</Syntax>
    <Example>= XOR(50,79)</Example>
  </XOR>
  <YEAR>
    <Description>Returns the YEAR corresponding to a date. The year is returned as an integer in the range 1900-9999.</Description>
    <Syntax>YEAR(serial_number)</Syntax>
    <Example>=YEAR(E1)</Example>
  </YEAR>
  <YEARFRAC>
    <Description>The YEARFRAC function returns the fraction of a year that is represented by the number of whole days between two supplied dates.</Description>
    <Syntax>YEARFRAC(startDate, endDate, [basis]) </Syntax>
    <Example>=YEARFRAC(C5,C6)</Example>
  </YEARFRAC>
  <Z.TEST>
    <Description>Returns the one-tailed P-value of a Z.TEST.</Description>
    <Syntax>Z.TEST(array, x, [sigma])</Syntax>
    <Example>=Z.TEST(A2:A9,4)</Example>
  </Z.TEST>
  <ZTEST>
    <Description>Returns the one-tailed probability-value of a ZTEST. </Description>
    <Syntax>ZTEST(array, u, sigma)</Syntax>
    <Example>=ZTEST(A4:A9,4)</Example>
  </ZTEST>
</Formulas>